Yaaaaaah!
50 years have passed,
but I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering
continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Gotta get back,
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
Aaaaaaaakuuuuuuuuuu.
Seven daughters
to do your bidding, Master.
They will succeed where
so many others have failed,
and we will find favor
in your glory.
Why?
Why have you forsaken us?
Have you forgotten,
my son?
No. No.
Help!
Help me, son!
You must!
Son,
you are forgetting us!
No.
You --
You never came back.
You left us.
You abandoned
your purpose.
I haven't!
You left us all to...
Die!
Ahh!
Son?
Father?
Why?
I -- I --
We've been waiting for you
so long,
but you never came back.
No, Father, Aku destroyed
the way home.
I don't understand!
You were the only one
who could save us!
Father.
He destroyed everything!
Everything is burning!
You've forgotten
your purpose!
You've forsaken us!
Ahh!
Ugh!
Any mistake is
certain death,
and death
is our failure.
Bask in the glory of
what our master has created.
Admire its beauty,
but know that the Samurai
is out there
leaving a wake of devastation
wherever he goes.
That's why, my sweet Ashi,
the daughters of Aku
must stay focused,
never relent,
always attack.
Teach this one
a lesson.
Stop!
The weak
have no place with Aku.
Are you weak?
Are you weak?!
Ahh!
Yes.
Aku's fire stirs
inside all of you.
To defeat the one,
your senses must be sharp.
Their time is almost at hand.
Once they succeed,
you will again honor us
with your presence.
Samurai Jack!
Man, it is good to see you,
babe.
What took you so long?
I decimated this village
days ago
just for you.
Oh, wait.
This is you, right?
I mean,
who could recognize you
with all that gear
and ruggedness, baby?
I'll tell you who --
me.
Scaramouch the Merciless,
the Pied Piper of Ruination,
the Crooner of Carnage,
the Ambassador of Annihilation,
the Eradicator of All, baby.
Also known as Aku's
most favorite assassin, babe.
Oh, there it is, babe,
the world-famous scowl.
Well, come on, Sammy, baby.
Whip it out.
You know what
I'm talking about --
that crazy sword.
Let's get slicin' and dicin',
swingin' and bashin',
hackin' and slashin',
babe.
Wait.
Back off, "Beardsly."
Where is your sword,
huh?
I don't see it.
Oh?
No, no, no, no, no,
babe!
Don't tell me
you lost your sword.
Okay, Jacky, baby,
you just make with the scowl
while I make with the phone
and call Aku.
Beep, beep, beep,
bo, dee, do, bip!
Who is this?!
Aku, baby,
how's it hanging, boss?
Guess what I --
What? Hello?!
Ooh,
nice choreography, babe.
You haven't lost a step.
Well, then, let's dance.
You know, babe, I wasn't crazy
about the front scruff,
but I am groovin'
on the mane.
Jack.
Help us, Jack.
Help us.
- Help us!
- Help us, Jack!
Please, no.
You must understand.
That samurai has gone
beaucoup cuckoo.
Hey, you might have destroyed
my magic flute,
but you can't destroy the
musical magic that is me, babe.
Dig that beautiful sound,
baby.
Hey, babe, I told you --
I'm Aku's favorite.
No one plays the blades
like I do.
No one!
Well, it's been fun, Jack-o,
but I got to move on.
Au revoir.
That's French for,
"You're dead, babe."
Well, babe, time for me
to shuffle offstage.
Looks like
you're the headliner now.
That's all, babe.
Ashi. Ashi.
Your training is complete.
Go! Kill!
You are seven,
but now you wear
the face of one,
one purpose for which
you were born --
to kill the Samurai!
* Watch out
* Gotta get back
* Back to the past
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Gotta get back,
back to the past, Samurai Jack *
* Watch out
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack
* Gotta get back
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out